{
    "id": "da2cb49322384a7d9ef72b9f2ea76d6d",
    "title": "Continuous And Non-continuous Verbs",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ef0b053b005e4583904882ca56e6e2eb",
            "title": "Continuous And Non-continuous Verbs",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I ……………………….. doubtful about the new plan.",
                    "description": "When feel means have an opinion, it is not used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "feel",
                        "am feeling",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………………… this scenery.",
                    "description": "The verb love is not normally used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "am loving",
                        "love",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………………. fine.",
                    "description": "To talk about feelings that are going on, we can use the simple and continuous forms of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "feel",
                        "am feeling",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………… your mother tomorrow.",
                    "description": "See has a continuous form when it is used to talk about a pre-planned future event. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "am seeing",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………… you have a problem with me.",
                    "description": "When see means understand it is not used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "am seeing",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "That creature …………………………. like a rabbit.",
                    "description": "When look means seem, it is not used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "looks",
                        "is looking",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………… that you are quitting your job.",
                    "description": "The word hear is not normally used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "hear",
                        "am hearing",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………… of writing a novel.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "think",
                        "am thinking",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………………….. we should not do it.",
                    "description": "When think means have an opinion, it is not used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "think",
                        "am thinking",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………… with the argument that education should be free for all.",
                    "description": "The verb agree is not normally used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "agree",
                        "am agreeing",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We may or may not go. It …………………………. on the weather.",
                    "description": "The verb depend is not normally used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "is depending",
                        "depends",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I still ………………………… meeting the seer.",
                    "description": "Remember is not normally used in the continuous form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "am remembering",
                        "remember",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}